Koji Satake. I'm looking forward to our game today.
I'm Nozomi Date. Glad to finally meet you. Good luck.
You know, you are the type of midfielder I love to watch during a game.
So focused. Always the calm, intelligent playmaker.
I get a little embarrassed when someone brings up my playing days.
Were you in J League too?
If you count the handful of games in J3 I played.
Well, regardless, you built a wonderful team here.
It's wild to think that these were the lesser-known players at one time. You've really done some great work.
Helps that I relate to them. I know what it's like to never be seen as the star player. Too well.
Tachivana!
Hey, guys!
I can't believe you never came to visit us. You're playing, right?
Yeah, and looking forward to it.
It's great to see you after all this time. You're looking good.
Anyway, is everything okay with your teammates out there?
I've never seen anyone look so freaked out and panicked just while warming up.
That's it.
That's it. Warm-up's over. Both teams should return to your locker rooms immediately.
hey you guys go on in i'm gonna hang out with her for a few
what the heck is takashima doing seriously yep that really just happened
but why now he doesn't have very long
What's going on? Why is everyone so tense?
I don't remember the last time I saw you all so nervous.
Well, anyways, be sure to use the countermeasures we've been working on this past week from the very start.
It would be a shame if you were all too tense to benefit from your hard work.
Individually, you guys are better than them. Don't forget that out there.
Please don't say that. It's bad luck to hear before a game.
Yeah, you basically just pep-talked us into losing.
It's because we're better individually that we are terrified of losing to them as a team.
I don't know what will happen to us after!
As usual, you're all useless and incompetent.
Hey, listen up. I have some advice for-
Hey, I'm back. Sorry it took so long.
I'm good now.
Thanks, Ty. I can tell you're a barber's daughter.
So, Takashima, is there a story behind your new look?
Nah, just tradition. It's what you do if you have a red pompadour.
Apparently, shaving it off helps to psych you up.
How do I look?
Wait, for real? You shaved off your hair right before a game? No way!
I had to do something about your pathetic faces.
This isn't an easy game for us.
We need to go out psyched.
Takashima's right, you guys.
The fact is, we've done everything we can.
We're way below Musashino in the league.
That makes us underdogs.
But that doesn't mean we can't win today!
And we're going to!
Yeah! Let's do it, guys!
He's right! Bring it on!
Togashima, remember what you said when you were on the junior team?
You were right all along, you know?
Winning should always be the priority.
Think about it.
If we don't win, then neither of you get to be right.
And it doesn't matter.
So let's win.
It's finally here.
The moment I've been waiting for.
We want the Musashino countermeasure in full gear from kickoff.
You got that?
Take a good look at them over there.
We know every single one of them.
And we've been showing them how much better we are than them since we were children.
Play the same game we always have and we can't lose!
Yeah!
There it is! The high press!
Hurry up! This way!
He rushed them just to play it backwards?
Put some pressure on him!
They're amazing. All of them.
I know, right?
Their strategy is predictable, though.
They're just hitting long balls.
Are they doing that on purpose?
Owie! Over to you!
It's true.
We thrive on our individual skills.
It's our advantage.
And if we lean on it more,
a simple tactic could work wonders.
Even against the high press,
we could take them by surprise.
What that means is,
if you want a shot at this,
brush up on your long ball technique.
Let me tell you something.
I don't have a lot of skills.
At all!
No matter how many times I stayed behind to practice,
I still sucked!
But you know what?
It'll help if you verbalize everything,
one long pass at a time.
And be sure to make eye contact.
Communicate with your eyes before you pass.
Every time.
They helped me practice,
and never gave up on me.
This long pass is for each of them.
And it's gonna make it all the way through.
Just approach the ball diagonally.
The toes of your planted foot
should always point where you want the ball.
Extend your toes and lock your ankle.
and then come down
and hit the middle of the ball
with the top of your foot.
The long ball got through!
He's clear the whole way!
For real?
Damn it!
Well, it looks like Asperion's tactic today
is trying to go direct.
They've chosen a style
that isn't so focused on retaining ball possession.
Going direct is a good call for them.
It's a proven formula against the high press.
All of Musashino's players
contribute to the high press.
So naturally,
that will help create numerous spaces
in their part of the field.
Then they'll be vulnerable.
With plenty of room for long balls
if all goes as planned.
Oh, it's gotta.
Coach Nozomi had them practicing long balls
for a whole week straight.
And like you pointed out,
they're like one-trick ponies.
I'm willing to bet a lot of teams
that face Musashino
will go with the same tactic.
However,
what sets Asperion apart from other teams is
their skill.
Hey, Ultimo!
Quit forcing it!
Pass it back!
Staying after training
wasn't such a bad idea.
I actually learned by teaching.
Like I was talking it through
and explaining it to myself.
It was also great to hear their ideas.
Spending time with them in that way
made all the difference.
Come on!
How'd I miss that?
Don't worry about it!
You'll get the next one!
It's working!
Musashino's high press can't function!
We've still got a chance to win!
They're not using this tactic as a group.
It's just all about making the most
of their individual strengths, right?
Yep!
Well, for the moment at least.
And that's it?
Huh?
One trick is all they've got.
Going with long balls, huh?
I honestly didn't expect
Esperion to fall back
on such a beginner tactic.
But you guys have some strong players
and you seem to have
a good flow on the field.
Well, sorta.
What's that mean?
I need you to deliver a message for me
to that loser player you have.
For it to work,
he needed to score back there.
But he couldn't seal the deal.
After the game,
he'll realize that was the fatal blow.
The one that ended it all.
Yeah!
Here comes the second attempt!
But first,
I gotta make eye contact.
Hit the middle of the ball.
The middle of the ball!
I can do this!
Boom!
There it is!
Nice. That's excellent space, Aoi. Way to go.
What? No way!
Damn, he stole it!
Hold it!
Togashi's amazing.
His kicks are powerful, but he keeps them smooth and controlled.
Nakano!
Man! That was so close!
If I hadn't brought him down...
Kahnata could have totally scored, just like he did then!
Sweet! Perfect place for a free kick!
They got a yellow card in the first 15 minutes?
How is that even possible?
Damn it!
Damn it! I'm so sorry!
Nah, man, don't sweat it! You were just trying to defend the best you could!
Hey, move more into the middle!
A yellow card!
I guess I need to be more careful!
But what was that?
Those two long balls earlier!
Five minutes ago, they would have gone through just fine!
Why not now? What happened?
Interesting!
They're leaving Tachibana and their number 12 up front!
They're gonna keep trying to counter it with a long ball!
So be on the lookout!
I don't know how long they've been planning it, but at least we know now!
Kaneda! Trust me! Do what I said!
I feel sick! Something's not right!
Those two! He and Kaneda were going at each other!
So what were they talking about?
Guys! Listen up! Use the direct approach all the way!
They can't counter our tactics!
Lean on your technique to punch through!
What? Going direct won't cut it!
It's not like that anymore!
Kodada?
Musashino's adjusted their tactics in the last few minutes!
That's their response to our direct approach!
They're gonna wait for us to step further back!
That means their reaction time will be intentionally shorter once the ball is kicked!
They've got us all figured out!
Five, six...
I don't get it! How did they adjust to make a new plan so quickly?
That guy! Number 10!
Chiaki Muto!
He's an incredible playmaker!
He... he's the playmaker?
Huh?
There's space out in front! Block it off!
He's in no rush. Instead of attacking, he calms the team down by playing back passes.
That was also his plan earlier, when they got the free kick in front of the goal. It was a huge opportunity to score. But Muto just went around talking to his teammates.
He was probably already telling them about the new game plan. His demeanor affects them. He makes the whole team calm. He's an excellent captain. And a brilliant playmaker!
We're only 17 minutes into the match. They're adjusting to our strategy too quickly. Damn it!
They're already starting to hesitate. Not good. They're in trouble.
Aspirion's got no one to calm them down.
What in the world is going on? Why is everyone's mood such trash? Did you all forget what we've been working on this entire week?
Come on, guys! Don't start doubting yourselves! We are going to win this!
You don't need to go out of your way to get the ball. We know they're going to screw up. That'll be your chance to shine.
Whoa! A short pass now, huh? Okay, I guess we'll just reset here and then...
I didn't kick hard enough!
That's what you think. Not on mine!
That was close.
Man! Screw this guy!
You can't just leave that monster unmarked. Not this time.
He knows where the ball's going.
That reaction to a passing error was insane.
His mid-range shots are crazy accurate. Dude can shoot from anywhere.
Just once. We mess up once and he gets to score. And it's bound to happen. As long as he's still around.
High press, without hesitation. Everyone working as a single unit.
One playmaker to coordinate them. And one pure striker.
We have everything Aspirion doesn't. Almost feels like an unfair advantage.
I think we should bring back man-marking. Because that guy can't be trusted.
Of course he's getting aggressive. Now that our long balls aren't working. Before anything else, we seriously need to rethink our marking.
Hey guys! Listen! I want to take over marking Kaneda.
Positionally, I'm his matchup. So I'll mark him. It makes the most sense.
You only switched to playing defense recently. Do you even know how to man-mark properly? Be honest.
What the heck, man? Why are you fighting me on this?
Just let me do it. Huh?
Trust me. I need to do this.
Kaneda has sure grown a lot, hasn't he? Amazing. Remember tryouts last year?
That aggression was all that made him stand out. But his technique and speed have improved.
His build is quite impressive. All that progress has increased his confidence.
That's important for our defense. But no need to worry. When it's about playing soccer,
our players have all the skills to back it up. I know they do.
Uh-huh. Long ball incoming! Be careful!
What? They've adjusted their play. Stopped relying on long balls. Now they're playing more short passes.
We have to remember that possession soccer is a spirion specialty. What's the best way to handle this?
Saki! Incoming! Got it!
Nakano! Hit Takaneda!
Yes!
Are they for real? That little guy is marking him? I don't think this is going to end very well.
Positioning is the most important thing in man-to-man marking. No question there.
Always keep a good distance from your opponent. You have to be able to observe his movement,
so you can predict what he'll do next. And then... Take it! Come on!
Physique differences don't matter. When it comes to the basic skills,
a spirion is the best. It looks like other players are adjusting now too, using short passes.
They just have to play their game. If they do, there's no way we're gonna lose today.
It's Tsukishima. Huh?
A real-life game doesn't play out the way you think it will on paper.
All right! Now to Kickstarter possession, sucker!
He's seriously fast! Huh? Whoa! And so is the little guy who's marking him!
KANIDAAA!
There you go! Pin him in there!
Quit making it so hard! This is supposed to be a game, a sport! I shouldn't have to deal with this
kind of hostility! Now move!
Nice!
The angle's too tight! There's no way!
Hey!
You pieces of shit!
HA!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ugh!
taught меня!
KANIDA!
ut
us
got
Aaron
us
an
We'll be right back.
Next time on Owlash, like a demon.